rockytravel.net 2015-12-06

# RockyTravel Privacy Policy : Rocky Travel

## Privacy Policy and Disclaimer of RockyTravel.net

### **TERMS OF USE  
**

Thank you for visiting www.rockytravel.net. All information are provided for general information purposes only. All statements represent our view and opinions. While we do our best to periodically update the information contained on Rocky Travel, we can not guarantee that the information provided on this website is correct, complete, and/or up-to-date. Furthermore we make no representations or warranties of any kind about the responsibility for the accuracy about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the information on this website. It is the responsibility of the user of this website to confirm the currency and validity of all information offered on this website. The materials contained on this website do not constitute legal, medical or other professional advice on any subject matter. www.rockytravel.net does not accept any responsibility for any loss which may arise from reliance on information, products, services, or related graphics contained on this site. You are reading of the information on this website is of your own free will and you are taking the provided information at your own risk.

#### Links to Third-Party Web Sites

Some links within this website may lead to other websites, including those operated and maintained by third parties. Rocky Travel includes these links solely as a convenience to you, and the presence of such a link does not imply a responsibility for the linked site or an endorsement of the linked site, its operator, or its contents. This website and its contents are provided “AS IS” without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement.

### COPYRIGHT POLICY

[Michela Fantine](http://www.rockytravel.net/about-me/)l is the legal copyright holder of the material on this website. All content, unless otherwise noted, may not be used, reprinted, or published in any form. Reproduction, distribution, republication, and/or retransmission of material, in form of content and images, contained within this website is not allowed without the written consent of Michela Fantinel from www.rockytravel.net.

### **PRIVACY POLICY**

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use www.rockytravel.net, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. Rocky Travel strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting my customers’, consumers’ and online visitors’ privacy on our website.

#### **Personal Information  
**

Rocky Travel collects personally identifiable information from the visitors only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number. This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other services or information from www.rockytravel.net. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.  
Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. Any personal information provided to us will be kept private. You will not be spammed in anyway and we will not sell or disclose your information to third-parties or any other companies.

#### **Non-personal Information  
**

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about my user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

#### **How you can correct or remove personal information  
**

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of my commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information to update, correct that information or delete that information please inform us throught [here](http://www.rockytravel.net/contact-us/ "Contact Us").

### ADVERTISERS

On some pages of this website we are using affiliate links and links or banners to our advertisers and sponsors. Affiliate links earn us a small commission on any purchase that anyone makes after clicking on on of our links. This help us cover the cost of running the site and expand our site. We only provide with valuable products that we find useful. We also provide our honest reviews and posts about products that we have tested. We will disclose whether we will be receiving money or commissions. We are not responsible for the actions of our advertisers or affiliate companies. If you purchase a product or service based upon a link from our website, you must take action directly with that company to resolve the issue.

### **USE OF COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS**

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable my system to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site’s services, a cookie enables Rocky Travel to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site. A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site. We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on my website to ascertain how many times you’ve seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on my web site. Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit websites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [Click Here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn’t cause a problem with my site, should you so choose.

### **RESERVE RIGHTS, UPDATES AND EFFECTIVE DATE**

We reserve the right to change the information, the focus of this website as well as change the terms of use  of this website at any time. Rocky Travel reserves the right to make changes in this policy too. We encourage you to periodically review our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy page.

### Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to Rocky Travel’s Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site. Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this disclaimer policy.

For any questions or concern please contact info (at) rockytravel (dot) net

[Leave Rocky Travel® Privacy Policy and Disclaimer and return to the Home Page](http://www.rockytravel.net/ "HomePage")

This post is also available in Italian and German
